reachoo.com 2010-12-22

# Reachoo free classifieds - ad syndication | policies

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Reachoo we have a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * We don't send your information for marketing purposes.
  * In our video classified products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals: 

Reachoo LLC. (“Reachoo”) only operates Reachoo.com. It is Reachoo’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Reachoo collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Reachoo’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Reachoo’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Reachoo may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Reachoo also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Reachoo does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Reachoo’s websites choose to interact with Reachoo in ways that require Reachoo to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Reachoo gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. In each case, Reachoo collects such information only in so far as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Reachoo. Reachoo does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

Reachoo may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Reachoo may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Reachoo does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Reachoo discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Reachoo’s behalf or to provide services available at Reachoo’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Reachoo’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Reachoo will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Reachoo discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Reachoo believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Reachoo, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Reachoo website and have supplied your email address, Reachoo may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Reachoo and our products. We primarily use our various video classifieds to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Reachoo takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Reachoo uses cookies to help Reachoo identify and track visitors, their usage of Reachoo website, and their website access preferences. Reachoo visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Reachoo’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Reachoo’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Reachoo may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Reachoo’s sole discretion. Reachoo encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Reachoo.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

Copyright © 2008-2009 Reachoo LLC. Privacy Policy.
